# dsv-docs

Homer does not publish this file for viewing by customers. This file informs Thycotic staff about this repository.

This repository contains technical documentation for **DevOps Secrets Vault** (DSV) and its ancillaries.

# DevOps Secrets Vault Technical Documentation

Two top-level folders separate product and ancillary content:

* the **product** folder houses content about DSV itself

* the **extensions** folder collects content about elements external to DSV such as extensions and plug-ins

## Document Contact

For content-related inquiries and concerns, contact:

David Buck  
Technical Writer, Product Management  
david.buck@thycotic.com  

For management-related considerations, contact:

Daniela Gran  
Director of Technical Publications, Product Management  
daniela.gran@thycotic.com    
_____________

© 2019-2020 Thycotic Software, LLC
