# dsv-docs/extensions

This second-level folder of the **DevOps Secrets Vault** technical documentation repository contains documentation on DSV extensions. This folder does not correspond to the URL where its contents will be published. The content of this folder will publish at URLs fitting the form https://docs.thycotic.com/dsv-extension-jenkins, with the name Jenkins being variable to match the specific company or product name related to the extension.

For core product documentation, see the **dsv-docs/product** folder.

# DevOps Secrets Vault Ancillaries Documentation

As published, content in this **dsv-docs/extensions** folder appears as product-related material available via the primary site’s **Related Docs** button, while content in the **dsv-docs/product** folder forms the primary documentation site for DevOps Secrets Vault.

## Document Contact

For content-related inquiries and concerns, contact:

David Buck  
Technical Writer, Product Management  
david.buck@thycotic.com  
206-574-8159

For management-related considerations, contact:

Tucker Hall  
Senior Director, Product Operations  
tucker.hall@thycotic.com  
917-498-0018  
_____________
David Buck
© 2019 Thycotic Software, LLC
